Thank you very much.
I'm going to the toilet.
I spent a lot of time.
I'm glad I like baseball.
Hello, I'm Kumi Sasaki.
I can see a little bit.
Where am I now?
The answer is...
Do you know?
Ta-da!
I'm in Seattle!
I'm here to watch the All-Star Game at
the MLB Stadium.
Wow!
This is the song I made.
I hope I can show you what Seattle is
like on this video.
Please enjoy the video until the end.
It's quite cold in Seattle.
It's before 12 o'clock.
I'm wearing long sleeves, but I'm still
cold.
I heard that clam chowder is delicious
in Seattle.
I'm going to eat clam chowder.
I'm at the public market center.
My dream,
Ta-da!
Pike Place Chowder
It's hot
It's so big
It's good
It's so good
It has a strong saltiness
But it has a lot of ingredients
It has a strong taste of seafood
It is very delicious
The taste of the pork cutlet is
delicious
The best
I'm hungry.
Thank you for the meal.
I can see the Ferris wheel.
I'm heading to the aquarium now.
I can smell the aquarium.
Ta-da!
I arrived at Seattle Park Avenue.
There are many exhibits.
I can see many things, not only fish.
What is this?
I found octopus.
It's too big!
It's so big!
I'm scared.
It's too big.
Is it coming here?
It's coming here.
It came here.
I'm scared.
I'm going home!
I can't believe it!
Oh no, they're getting closer.
Oh my god!
They're here!
So cute!
They're so cute!
They're so cute.
They're coming closer.
So cute!
Look at their faces!
They're so cute!
I'm going to see the Japanese version of
this tomorrow.
Ta-da!
This is a uniform and a hat from All-
Star.
It's cute!
I'm going to experience the batting
practice.
I'm going to join the practice with
these people.
It's a batting practice.
She is a professional.
I put on a glove.
The athlete matches her tactic and
height condition to obtain points.
But, she loses the race.
The next station is Boston-Red Sox,
along the Yorkshire line.
Doors are closing on the right.
I'm not sure if I can get in.
I believe so.
Do you see everyone coming out of there?
Oh, got it.
I'm just at the first floor.
But I can't get in.
I'm not sure if I can get in.
I'm satisfied just standing in this
queue.
I'm going to the pitching club.
Can I do it?
Thunder did reach there.
What's happening?
Hina-chan from Sodom
Wow, I shocked with power.
17єv。
Second match
Soulg participant Rie
Anxious
Wow
I'm going to win!
Ichido!
Thank you!
I'm going to win!
It was a pretty easy game.
My pleasure.
Thank you.
I'm going to win!
I finished my practice.
It's breakfast time.
I'm eating a hamburger with a logo of
Manila in it.
I got a souvenir like this.
And I got this.
What is this?
Is this me?
I was so nervous that I was putting on a
shield before I practiced batting.
I was so nervous at that time.
I will treasure this moment forever.
I spent too much time for this moment.
I'm so glad that I love baseball.
I'm back at the red carpet.
I'm here to talk to the players.
I'm nervous because I'm afraid that I'll
be taken a picture.
I'm wearing the hat of Angel to catch
the eye of the other players.
I'm so nervous.
I'll do my best.
I'm nervous because I'm afraid that I'll
be taken a picture.
Nérois!
this is so cute
cheers
is it good ?
the rest of the family is tiring
you can capture the feeling bring on
this Instagram
should i take a picture of him
ah ! yes
take a picture of him
how is that ?
thank you
Ta-da!
I'm at Space Needle!
I heard that I can see the whole city of
Seattle from here, so I'm going to climb
up!
I climbed up Space Needle!
Wow!
I can see the whole city of Seattle from
here!
Wow!
This is downtown.
I can see the airport I went to.
I can see the whole city of Seattle.
We are...
Ready?
And with the first overall pick of the
2023 MLB Draft, the Los Angeles Angels
select pitcher and outfielder, Kumi
Sasaki!
50 spiciness
Insane?!
2opc was born.
With huge spectators.
National Team
Mr hotani
donít wait for me!
Woah!
Bravo!
The number of people is increasing.
Dance on Midway.
I lost the American League, but I'm very
happy.
It was a fun game!